let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Who is Harry Potter's godfather?",
        answer: "Sirius Black",
        options: [
           "Sirius Black",
           "Remus Lupin", 
           "Peter Pettigrew", 
           "Severus Snape"   
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What was the name of the tree Harry and Ron crashed their car into?",
        answer: "The Whomping Willow",
        options: [
           "Mandrake", 
           "Gillyweed", 
           "The Whomping Willow",
           "Shrivelfig"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which class has a different teacher every year?",
        answer: "Defence against the dark arts",
        options: [
           "Transfiguration", 
           "Herbology", 
           "Potions", 
           "Defence against the dark arts"  
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the name of Hermione's pet cat?",
        answer: "CrookShanks",
        options: [
           "Padfoot",
           "CrookShanks", 
           "Fawkes",
           "Norbert"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Where is Azkaban located?",
        answer: "The North Sea",
        options: [
           "The North Sea",
           "The South Sea",
           "The East Sea", 
           "The West Sea"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What is the name of the train that takes students to Hogwarts?",
        answer: "The Hogwarts Express",
        options: [
           "9 3/4 Express", 
           "Enchanted Express", 
           "The Magical Express",
           "The Hogwarts Express"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What subject does Hagrid teach?",
        answer: "Care of Magical Creatures",
        options: [
           "Charms",
           "Care of Magical Creatures",
           "History of Magic",
           "Astronomy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "How did Harry and Ron get to Hogwarts their second year?",
        answer: "Flying Car",
        options: [
           "Flying Car",
           "Portkey", 
           "Train", 
           "Broomstick"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What is Tom Riddleâ€™s middle name?",
        answer: "Marvolo",
        options: [
            "John", 
            "James", 
            "Marvolo",
            "Bilius"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which type of insect is Ron Weasley most afraid of?",
        answer: "Spiders",
        options: [
           "Weevils", 
           "Spiders",
           "Beetles", 
           "Mosquitoes"
        ]
    }
]